HEY, YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO BELIEVE THIS.
I MADE UP A JOKE
AND SENT IT IN TO PLAYBOY.
THEY PRINTED IT.
I DIDN'T KNOW PLAYBOY
PRINTS JOKES.
YEAH, THEY PRINT JOKES,
UH, INTERVIEWS
HARD-HITTING JOURNALISM.
IT'S NOT JUST
ABOUT THE PICTURES.
IT DIDN'T
WORK ON MOM.
IT'S NOT GOING
TO WORK ON US.
HERE, CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S THE FIRST ONE, TOO.
RIGHT THERE.
( all chuckling )
THAT IS FUNNY.
IT WAS ALSO FUNNY
WHEN I MADE IT UP.
WHAT?
I MADE THAT JOKE UP.
UH, OH, NO, YOU DIDN'T. I DID.
UH-UH-OH, YES, I DID.
I TOLD IT TO DAN AT WORK
AND HE SAID IT WAS
THE FUNNIEST JOKE
HE'D EVER HEARD.
HEY, TELL DAN "THANKS."
WHAT?
I'M SORRY. I WAS JUST READING
THE JOKE BELOW IT.
THAT ONE IS FUNNY.
MONICA, YOU REMEMBER ME
TELLING YOU THAT JOKE, RIGHT?
NO.
SERIOUSLY?
WELL, YOU TELL
A LOT OF JOKES.
LOOK, CHANDLER,
IT'S MY JOKE.
HEY, IF IT MAKES YOU
FEEL ANY BETTER
THEY DON'T PRINT THE NAME,
SO IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER
WHO GETS CREDIT, RIGHT?
I GUESS NOT.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY, JOEY!
PLAYBOY PRINTED MY JOKE!
NO! NO! IT'S MY MINE!
IT'S MY JOKE!
YOU CAN CALL THEM.
THEY'LL TELL YOU.
IT'S MY JOKE.
IT'S MY JOKE!
WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
JOKES?
YOU GUYS KNOW THEY HAVE
NAKED CHICKS IN THERE, RIGHT?
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
DUDE, DUDE, YOU HAVE GOT TO
TURN ON BEHIND THE MUSIC.
THE BAND HEART IS HAVING
A REALLY TOUGH TIME
AND I THINK THEY
MAY BREAK UP.
HEY, LET'S GO WATCH
THAT AT YOUR PLACE.
NO, NO, NO, MONICA'S WATCHING
SOME COOKING SHOW.
COME ON, I DON'T WANT TO MISS
WHEN THEY WERE SKINNY.
UH, HEY-HEY,
CHANDLER, CHANDLER
YOU KNOW WHAT
WE SHOULD DO?
YOU AND I SHOULD GO OUT
AND GET SOME NEW SUNGLASSES.
WHAT? NO.
I WANT TO WATCH THIS.
DID YOUR CABLE GO OUT?
NO, NO. THAT'S VH1. YEAH.
I GOT TO TELL YOU, THE MUSIC
THESE KIDS LISTEN TO TODAY
IT'S LIKE A LOT OF NOISE
TO ME. I DON'T KNOW.
JOEY, WHY IS YOUR CABLE OUT?
UH...
OH, BECAUSE
I HAVEN'T REALLY
PAID THE BILL.
LOOK, IF YOU NEED MONEY
WOULD YOU PLEASE, PLEASE
JUST LET ME LOAN YOU
SOME MONEY?
NO, CHANDLER.
LOOK, FORGET ABOUT IT, OKAY?
LOOK, I KNOW THINGS HAVE
BEEN A LITTLE TIGHT
SINCE JANINE MOVED OUT--
GOD, WAS SHE HOT.
WHOA-HO.
I KNOW.
BUT LOOK, I CAN
HANDLE IT, ALL RIGHT?
I CAN... LISTEN
TO THE RADIO, HUH?
AND, UH, HEY, ROSS GAVE
ME THIS GREAT BOOK.
OKAY, FINE. YOU WANT TO SEE
IF THE JOKE STEALER
WILL LET US WATCH THE SHOW
AT HIS PLACE?
SURE. YEAH.
PAID YOUR PHONE BILL?
NOT SO MUCH.
HEY.
IT'S ONLY YOU.
WH-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE ARE LOOKING
AT A PLAYBOY.
OH, I WANT TO LOOK, TOO.
YIKES!
( laughs )
SO DO YOU THINK
THAT THESE PICTURES...
ARE THEY TRYING
TO TELL A STORY?
OH, WELL, YEAH, SURE.
I MEAN, LIKE IN THE CASE
OF THIS YOUNG WOMAN
SHE HAS LOST HER
CLOTHES, SO...
SO SHE RIDES NAKED ON THE
HORSE, SHE'S CRYING OUT
"WHERE ARE THEY?
WHERE ARE THEY?"
WELL, SHE'S NOT GOING
TO FIND THEM
LYING IN THE GRASS
LIKE THAT.
( laughing )
GOD...
OH... YEAH.
OH, REMEMBER THE DAYS
WHEN YOU USED TO GO OUT
TO THE BARN
LIFT UP YOUR SHIRT
AND BEND OVER?
YEAH.
YOU SEE, NOW...
SEE, NOW, I WOULD
DATE THIS GIRL.
SHE'S CUTE;
SHE'S OUTDOORSY.
YOU KNOW, AND SHE KNOWS
HOW TO BUILD A FIRE.
I MEAN, THAT'S GOT
TO COME IN HANDY.
HEY, I GOT A QUESTION.
MM-HMM?
IF YOU HAD TO PICK ONE OF US
TO DATE, WHO WOULD IT BE?
I DON'T KNOW.
ME, NEITHER.
RACHEL.
WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
ME, NEITHER.
YOU KNOW, YOU FORGET
HOW MANY GREAT SONGS HEART HAD.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, "BARRACUDA" WAS
THE FIRST SONG I LEARNED
TO PLAY ON THE KEYBOARD.
SO YOU HEARD IT,
YOU REPEATED IT...
SO THAT MUST MEAN...
YOU WROTE IT.
OH, YOU GUYS WITH THIS JOKE.
LOOK, I GOT TO SAY,
I KNOW I CRACKED UP
BUT I'M NOT EVEN SURE I GOT IT.
WHAT?
YOU DIDN'T GET IT?
THE DOCTOR IS A MONKEY.
( both laughing )
AND MONKEYS CAN'T
WRITE OUT PRESCRIPTIONS.
( both laughing )
YOU ARE NOT ALLOWED
TO LAUGH AT MY JOKE.
YOUR JOKE?
WELL, I THINK THE
HEF WOULD DISAGREE
WHICH IS WHY HE SENT
ME A CHECK FOR $100.
SO YOU STOLE MY JOKE,
AND YOU STOLE MY MONEY?
YOU KNOW... I WAS GOING TO
STICK IT IN THE ATM
BUT NOW I THINK I'LL
SHOW THE SEXY TELLER
THAT I AM A PUBLISHED WRITER.
WELL, SHE IS GOING TO KNOW
THAT YOU STOLE THE JOKE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO,
FOLLOW ME DOWN THERE?
YEAH.
WELL, I'M NOT GOING
TO GO NOW ANYWAY.
OKAY.
HERE YOU GO.
OH.
UH...
UH, GUNTHER...
I CAN'T PAY FOR
THIS RIGHT NOW
'CAUSE, UH,
I'M NOT WORKING
SO I'VE HAD TO CUT DOWN ON
SOME LUXURIES LIKE, UH...
PAYING FOR STUFF, SO...
WELL... IF YOU WANT,
YOU CAN WORK HERE.
UH, I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S, UH, IT'S JUST...
SEE, I WAS A REGULAR
ON A SOAP OPERA, YOU KNOW...
AND TO GO FROM THAT TO THIS,
IT'S JUST...
AND PLUS, YOU KNOW, I'D HAVE
TO WAIT ON ALL MY FRIENDS.
OKAY, BUT THE MONEY'S GOOD.
PLUS YOU GET TO STARE AT RACHEL
AS MUCH AS YOU WANT.
WHAT?
FLEXIBLE HOURS.
OH.
MAYBE I COULD
BE A WAITER.
COULD I USE THE PHONE?
SHE PICKED RACHEL.
I MEAN, SHE TRIED
TO BACK OUT OF IT
BUT IT WAS OBVIOUS--
SHE PICKED RACHEL.
HE TOOK MY JOKE;
HE J-JUST TOOK IT.
THAT'S WRONG.
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
IS WRONG?
PHOEBE PICKING RACHEL.
YOU KNOW WHO ELSE
PICKED RACHEL?
ROSS. YOU KNOW
WHAT ELSE ROSS DID?
HE STOLE MY JOKE.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M
GOING TO GET A JOKE
JOURNAL, YOU KNOW?
AND DOCUMENT THE
DATE AND TIME
OF EVERY SINGLE
ONE OF MY JOKES.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S
A BAD IDEA?
PICKING RACHEL.
THAT'S RIGHT.
DID YOU HEAR SOMETHING?
WELL, MAYBE IT'S
THE SOUND OF ROSS
CLIMBING INTO MY BRAIN
AND STEALING MY THOUGHTS.
I THINK IT'S COMING
FROM THE LIVING ROOM.
I FINISHED MY BOOK.
( knocking on door )
HEY, YOU GUYS.
HEY.
OH, DON'T YOU GUYS LOOK CUTE.
YOU GUYS MAKE
SUCH A CUTE COUPLE.
MONICA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NOTHING. I'M JUST TRYING
TO RECREATE SOME OF THE FUN
THAT WE HAD AT MY PLACE
THE OTHER DAY.
REMEMBER? WHEN YOU PICKED RACHEL
OVER ME?
( laughing ):
THAT WAS FUNNY.
YES, IT WAS KIND OF FUNNY.
IT WASN'T FUNNY AT ALL.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
WHY DIDN'T YOU PICK ME?
FINE.
THE REASON THAT I WAS LEANING
A LITTLE BIT MORE
TOWARD RACHEL THAN YOU
IS JUST, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE...
KIND OF HIGH MAINTENANCE.
OKAY, LET'S GO TO LUNCH.
THAT... THAT IS
COMPLETELY UNTRUE.
YOU THINK
I'M HIGH MAINTENANCE?
OKAY, PROVE IT--
I WANT YOU TO WRITE OUT A LIST
AND WE'RE GOING TO GO THROUGH IT
POINT BY POINT.
NO, YOU'RE RIGHT--
YOU'RE EASYGOING.
YOU'RE JUST NOT
AS EASYGOING AS RACHEL.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S JUST
MORE... FLEXIBLE
AND-AND MELLOW, THAT'S ALL.
WELL, PEOPLE ARE DIFFERENT.
YEAH, YOU KNOW, RACHEL--
SHE'LL DO WHATEVER YOU WANT,
YOU KNOW?
YOU CAN JUST WALK ALL OVER HER.
WHAT? WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT, ARE YOU SAYING
I'M A PUSHOVER?
I'M NOT A PUSHOVER.
OH, OKAY.
YOU'RE NOT A PUSHOVER.
OH, MY... YOU THINK
I'M A PUSHOVER.
WELL, WATCH THIS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE NOT INVITED TO LUNCH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT?
I THINK THAT'S PRETTY
STRONG, IS WHAT I THINK.
COME ON, MONICA,
LET'S GO TO LUNCH.
YOU START WORKING
ON THAT LIST!
I CANNOT BELIEVE HER.
I KNOW.
WHERE DO YOU WANT
TO GO EAT?
OH... OH!
I LOVE THAT JAPANESE PLACE.
I'M SICK OF JAPANESE.
WE'RE NOT GOING THERE.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, WHEREVER
YOU WANT TO GO IS COOL.
OH, HEY, GUNTHER
CHECK THIS OUT.
( laughing )
YEAH, THAT CHANDLER
CRACKS ME UP.
HEY, ROSS, LISTEN,
YOU WANT ANYTHING TO DRINK?
'CAUSE I'M HEADING UP THERE.
UH, YEAH, I'LL
TAKE A COFFEE.
THANKS, MAN.
SURE.
COFFEE?
NO.
COFFEE? 'CAUSE
I'M GOING UP THERE.
OH, NO, THANK YOU.
OKAY.
YOU GUYS NEED ANYTHING?
'CAUSE I'M HEADING UP THERE.
I'D LOVE A... ICE WATER.
( chuckling ):
YOU GOT IT.
JOEY... WHAT
ARE YOU DOING?
( chuckling ):
JUST BEING FRIENDLY.
JOEY, I-I DON'T THINK YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO GO BACK THERE.
NO, NO, IT'S OKAY.
RIGHT GUNTHER?
DON'T WINK AT ME.
AND PUT ON YOUR APRON.
( chuckling ):
OKAY.
I DON'T SEE YOU ASKING
ANY OTHER PAYING CUSTOMERS
TO PUT ON APRONS.
JOEY... DO YOU WORK HERE?
NO.
WAITER?
YEAH?
JOEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL
US YOU WORK HERE?
WELL...
WELL... IT'S KIND OF
EMBARRASSING, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, I WAS AN ACTOR;
NOW I'M A WAITER.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO GO
IN THE OTHER DIRECTION.
SO IS YOUR APRON--
YOU'RE WEARING IT LIKE A CAPE.
I MEAN, THE JOB'S EASY,
AND THE MONEY'S GOOD, YOU KNOW
AND I GUESS IF I'M GOING
TO BE HANGING OUT HERE ANYWAY
I MIGHT AS WELL GET PAID
FOR IT, RIGHT?
I JUST FEEL KIND OF WEIRD
SERVING YOU GUYS, YOU KNOW?
IT'LL BE GREAT.
OH...
JOEY, COME ON,
I DID IT
AND IT WAS FINE.
YEAH. WHY WOULD IT BE WEIRD?
HEY, JOEY, UH,
COULD I GET SOME COFFEE?
OKAY, I GUESS IT DOESN'T
SEEM THAT WEIRD.
SERIOUSLY, I ASKED YOU BEFORE--
YOU STILL HAVEN'T GOTTEN IT.
SEE, NOW IT'S WEIRD AGAIN.
I THINK IT'S GREAT
THAT YOU WORK HERE.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE A LOT OF
MONEY AND HERE'S YOUR FIRST TIP:
DON'T EAT YELLOW SNOW.
( chuckling )
2:15. COFFEE HOUSE.
WELL, YOU KNOW, THIS IS GREAT--
FINALLY, I HAVE SOMEONE
I CAN PASS ON MY WISDOM TO.
LET ME TELL YOU
ABOUT A COUPLE THINGS I LEARNED
WHILE WORKING
AT THE COFFEE HOUSE.
UM, FIRST OF ALL, THE
CUSTOMER IS ALWAYS RIGHT;
A SMILE GOES A LONG WAY;
AND IF ANYONE
IS EVER RUDE TO YOU...
SNEEZE MUFFIN.
THANKS, RACH.
HEY, LOOK, YOU GUYS
ARE JUST TERRIFIC, YOU KNOW?
NOW, HOW ABOUT
CLEARING OUT OF HERE
SO I CAN GET
SOME NEW CUSTOMERS, HUH?
IT'S ALL ABOUT TURNOVER.
( laughs )
JOEY...
SERIOUSLY,
CAN I GET MY COFFEE?
OH, I'M SORRY, ROSS.
I'LL GET IT FOR
YOU RIGHT NOW.
AND SINCE I MADE YOU WAIT,
I'LL TOSS IN A FREE MUFFIN.
PHOEBE, WE WOULD LIKE
TO TALK TO YOU FOR A SECOND.
OKAY.
SO...
MAYBE I AM A LITTLE
HIGH MAINTENANCE
AND MAYBE RACHEL IS
A LITTLE BIT OF A PUSHOVER
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT
WE DECIDED THAT YOU ARE?
YES, WE ARE VERY SORRY
TO TELL YOU THIS
BUT YOU, PHOEBE, ARE FLAKY.
HA!
THAT'S TRUE.
I AM FLAKY.
SO, WHAT?
YOU'RE JUST, UH,
YOU'RE JUST OKAY
WITH BEING FLAKY?
YEAH, TOTALLY.
WELL, THEN I'M OKAY
WITH BEING HIGH MAINTENANCE.
YEAH, AND I AM OKAY
WITH BEING A PUSHOVER.
THAT'S GREAT.
GOOD FOR YOU GUYS!
I AM NOT HIGH MAINTENANCE!
AND I AM NOT
A PUSHOVER!
WHO SAID YOU WERE?!
YOU DID!
I'M FLAKY.
I'LL SAY ANYTHING.
HEY, GUNTHER,
CAN YOU COVER FOR ME?
I JUST GOT AN AUDITION.
NO, I'M LEAVING
TO GET MY HAIR DYED.
REALLY? I LIKE
YOUR NATURAL COLOR.
COME ON, IT'S
A GREAT PART.
I'M THE LEAD GUY'S
BEST FRIEND
AND I WAIT FOR HIM
IN THIS BAR AND SAVE HIS SEAT.
LISTEN. LISTEN.
I'M SORRY. THAT SEAT'S SAVED.
THAT'S THE WHOLE PART?
OKAY, MAYBE HE'S NOT
HIS BEST FRIEND, BUT...
OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU
IN AN HOUR.
I COULD TOTALLY
GET THAT PART.
I'M SORRY,
THIS SEAT IS TAKEN.
OH, EXCUSE ME.
NO, NO, NO, I...
I DIDN'T MEAN YOU
BUT, UH, YOU BELIEVE ME, HUH?
I BELIEVED YOU WERE SAVING
THIS SEAT FOR SOMEONE.
SO YOU'D HIRE ME, RIGHT?
FOR WHAT?
EXACTLY!
ALL RIGHT, UH,
EVERYBODY, LISTEN UP.
THE COFFEEHOUSE
IS GOING TO BE
CLOSED FOR ABOUT AN HOUR.
All:
WHAT?!
WE JUST
GOT HERE.
YEAH, IT'S, UH,
IT'S FOR THE KIDS.
YEAH, TO, UH,
KEEP THE KIDS OFF DRUGS.
YUP, IT'S A VERY IMPORTANT ISSUE
IN THIS MONTH'S PLAYBOY.
I'M SURE YOU ALL READ ABOUT IT.
THERE YOU GO.
IT'S MY JOKE.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T
THINK WE'RE GOING
TO SETTLE THIS.
NO. LET'S HAVE
MONICA DECIDE.
YEAH.
HEY, MON!
MON, GET OUT HERE!
MONICA!
OKAY, OKAY.
YOU HAVE TO HELP US
DECIDE WHOSE JOKE THIS IS.
WHY DO I HAVE
TO DECIDE?
BECAUSE YOU'RE
THE ONLY ONE
THAT CAN BE FAIR.
I CAN'T BE FAIR.
YOU'RE MY BOYFRIEND.
YEAH, BUT I'M YOUR BROTHER.
WE'RE FAMILY.
THAT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
IN THE WORLD.
DON'T TRY TO SWAY HER.
I'M YOUR ONLY CHANCE
TO HAVE A BABY.
OKAY, LET'S GO.
ALL RIGHT, UM, OKAY,
WE'LL EACH TELL YOU
HOW WE CAME UP
WITH THE JOKE
AND THEN YOU DECIDE
WHICH ONE OF US
IS TELLING THE TRUTH-- ME.
CHANDLER, YOU GO FIRST.
OKAY, I THOUGHT
OF THE JOKE
TWO MONTHS AGO
AT LUNCH WITH STEVE.
IS HE THE GUY
I MET AT CHRISTMAS?
CAN I FINISH MY STORY?
DO YOU WANT ME TO PICK YOU?
SEE, I WOULD NEVER
SNAP AT YOU LIKE THAT.
CONTINUE.
OKAY, SO STEVE SAID
HE HAD TO GO TO THE DOCTOR
AND STEVE'S DOCTOR'S NAME
IS DR. MOMPEY.
SO I SAID, "DR. MONKEY?"
AND THAT IS HOW THE WHOLE
DR. MONKEY THING CAME UP.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
OKAY, LOOK, I STUDY
EVOLUTION.
REMEMBER? EVOLUTION?
MONKEY INTO MAN.
PLUS, I'M A DOCTOR
AND I HAD A MONKEY.
I'M DR. MONKEY!
I'M NOT ARGUING
WITH THAT.
I'VE HEARD ENOUGH.
I HAVE MADE MY DECISION.
( both grunting )
YOU ARE BOTH IDIOTS.
THE JOKE IS NOT FUNNY
AND IT'S OFFENSIVE TO WOMEN,
AND DOCTORS, AND MONKEYS.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE ARGUING
OVER WHO GETS CREDIT
YOU SHOULD BE ARGUING
OVER WHO GETS BLAMED
FOR INFLICTING THIS HORRIBLE
JOKE UPON THE WORLD.
NOW, LET IT GO.
THE JOKE SUCKS!
IT'S YOUR JOKE.
IT IS NOT.
MY GOD, CHANDLER,
THERE YOU ARE.
HI-I!
HEY, IT'S PHOEBE
AND RACHEL.
WHY DON'T YOU
TELL THEM
WHAT YOU WERE
TELLING ME EARLIER
ABOUT ME NOT BEING
HIGH MAINTENANCE.
MONICA IS A
SELF-SUFFICIENT,
TOGETHER LADY.
BEING WITH HER HAS
BEEN LIKE BEING
ON A VACATION.
AND WHAT MAY
BE PERCEIVED AS
HIGH MAINTENANCE
IS MERELY ATTENTION
TO DETAIL AND...
( mumbles )
GENEROSITY
OF SPIRIT.
WOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT IS THE BEST FAKE SPEECH
I THINK I'VE EVER HEARD.
REALLY? NO, I'VE HEARD BETTER.
WAIT. WAIT. HE CAME UP
WITH THAT HIMSELF.
TELL THEM, CHANDLER.
I'M OUT OF WORDS.
SHOULD I JUST SAY
THE WHOLE THING AGAIN?
I AM NOT HIGH MAINTENANCE.
I AM NOT.
CHANDLER!
YOU'RE A LITTLE
HIGH MAINTENANCE.
( gasps )
YOU ARE ON MY LIST.
LOOK, I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU'RE NOT EASYGOING
BUT YOU'RE PASSIONATE
AND THAT'S GOOD.
AND WHEN YOU GET UPSET
ABOUT THE LITTLE THINGS
I THINK THAT I'M PRETTY GOOD
AT MAKING YOU FEEL BETTER
ABOUT THAT.
AND THAT'S GOOD, TOO.
SO THEY CAN SAY
THAT YOU'RE HIGH MAINTENANCE
BUT IT'S OKAY
BECAUSE I LIKE...
MAINTAINING YOU.
I DIDN'T EVEN TELL
HIM TO SAY THAT.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE
OFF MY LIST.
I'M OFF THE LIST.
PHOEBE...
IT'S OKAY THAT YOU
DON'T WANT ME TO
BE YOUR GIRLFRIEND
BECAUSE I HAVE
THE BEST BOYFRIEND.
YOU KNOW, SUDDENLY
I FIND YOU VERY ATTRACTIVE.
HEY, BUDDY BOY,
HOW DID THE AUDITION GO?
OH, NOT GOOD.
I DIDN'T GET THE PART
AND, UH, LOST MY JOB HERE
SO...
WOW, THAT IS A BAD AUDITION.
HOW DID YOU LOSE YOUR JOB HERE?
WELL, I HAD THE AUDITION
BUT GUNTHER SAID I HAD
TO STAY HERE AND BE IN CHARGE
SO HE COULD GO
GET HIS HAIR DYED.
SO, I WENT ANYWAY
AND THEN HE FIRED ME.
HE LEFT WORK
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE DAY
TO DO A PERSONAL ERRAND
AND LEFT YOU IN CHARGE
WHEN YOU'VE BEEN WORKING HERE
FOR TWO DAYS.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
WELL, JOEY
YOU CAN'T LET HIM
GET AWAY WITH THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M NOT GOING
TO LET HIM GET AWAY WITH THAT.
I'M GOING TO SAY SOMETHING TO...
NO, I REALLY SHOULDN'T
SAY ANYTHING TO HIM.
NO, I SHOULD SAY
SOMETHING TO HIM!
GUNTHER, I WANT
YOU TO GIVE JOEY
HIS JOB BACK.
THAT IS REALLY NOT FAIR
THAT YOU HAVE TO FIRE...
OKAY.
WHAT?
HE CAN HAVE HIS JOB BACK.
THAT'S RIGHT HE CAN HAVE HIS...
JOB BACK.
GLAD WE GOT THAT
ALL STRAIGHTENED OUT.
THERE YOU GO, JOEY.
YOU GOT YOUR JOB BACK.
THAT'S GREAT.
THANKS, RACH.
YEAH, PRETTY NICE, HUH?
NOW WHO'S A PUSHOVER?
RACH, YOU'RE IN MY SEAT.
I'M SORRY.
HEY, I NEVER GOT TO HEAR
WHO YOU GUYS WOULD PICK
TO BE YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
OH, I'D PICK YOU,
PHOEBE.
OH, YEAH.
DEFINITELY
YOU, PHEEBS.
YEAH, WELL, I KIND OF THOUGHT.
HEY.
OH, HEY.
WAIT. I HAVE
A QUESTION.
IF ONE OF YOU
HAD TO PICK
ONE OF THE OTHER TWO
GUYS TO GO OUT WITH
WHO WOULD YOU PICK?
NO WAY.
I'M NOT ANSWERING THAT.
JOEY.
NO WAY.
I'M NOT ANSWERING THAT.